[{"id":341,"question":"What is the best way to change table prefix (wp_) before installation in WordPress?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Before Installation: In this way, you have to rename your wp_config.php file according to your need through $table_prefix=\u2019wp_\u2019;.","answer_b":"Before Installation: Through this way, you have to go PHPMyAdmin -> Select your database -> Check all tables -> Add\/Update table prefix.","answer_c":"After Installation: Once you have the database, you can go ahead and change it","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"WordPress"}],"category":"CMS","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":980,"question":"How do you call a function named \"myFunction\"?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"myFunction()","answer_b":"call myFunction()","answer_c":"call function myFunction()","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"JavaScript"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":951,"question":"Which statement is true for Replica set?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Replica set is considered as a substitute to the replication controller. The prime function of replica set is to assure the number of pod replicas running.","answer_b":"Replica set is considered as the legacy replication controller. The prime function of replica set is to remove the number of pod replicas running.","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":475,"question":"How can you make A bulleted list with numbers?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<dl>","answer_b":"<ul>","answer_c":"<ol>","answer_d":"<list>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":667,"question":"Choose the odd one out.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"csh","answer_b":"bsh","answer_c":"ksh","answer_d":"Kernel","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"true","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"Kernel is the core part of the OS and is odd one the rest are popular shells.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"BASH"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":966,"question":"What is the purpose of a ReplicaSet?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"To prevent clones from invading other clusters","answer_b":"To monitor and respond to environmental latency","answer_c":"To maintain a stable set of replica Pods running at any given time","answer_d":"To create and maintain volumes","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":232,"question":"Which of the following statements are true about SQL injection attacks?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Wrapping all variables containing user input by a call to mysql_real_escape_string() makes the code immune to SQL injections.","answer_b":"Parametrized queries do not make code less vulnearable to SQL injections.","answer_c":"SQL injections are not possible, if only emulated prepared statements are used.","answer_d":"Usage of later versions of MySQL, validation, and explicit setting of the charset of user input are valid measures to decrease vulnerability to SQL injections.","answer_e":"None of the above","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":224,"question":"Which command is used to specify the number of records to return?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"SELECT","answer_b":"SELECT TOP","answer_c":"EXTRACT","answer_d":"SELECT SPECIFIC","answer_e":"LIMIT","answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"true","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":148,"question":"Which doctype is correct for HTML5?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"<!DOCTYPE HTML5>","answer_b":"<!DOCTYPE HTML PUBLIC>","answer_c":"<!DOCTYPE html>","answer_d":"<HTML5>","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":77,"question":"Which one of these variables has an illegal name?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$myVar","answer_b":"$my_Var","answer_c":"$my-Var","answer_d":"$MyVar","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_c","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":773,"question":"Which of the following provides the error code associated with this file upload?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"$_FILES['file']['error']","answer_b":"$_FILES['file']['errors']","answer_c":"$_FILES['error']","answer_d":"$_FILES['errors']","answer_e":"$_FILES->file->error","answer_f":"$_FILES->file->errors"},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":"$_FILES['file']['error'] \u2212 it provides the error code associated with this file upload.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":623,"question":"How can the result set of Mysql be handled in PHP?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"The result set can be handled using mysqli_fetch_array, mysqli_fetch_assoc, mysqli_fetch_object or mysqli_fetch_row.","answer_b":"The result set can be handled using mysqli_get_array","answer_c":null,"answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":918,"question":"What did the 1.8 version of Kubernetes introduce?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"Taints and Tolerations","answer_b":"Cluster level","answer_c":"Logging Secrets","answer_d":"Federated Clusters","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":716,"question":"An abstraction in kubernetes which defines a logical set of pods and a policy to access them.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"node","answer_b":"cluster","answer_c":"service","answer_d":"set","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":"A service is a grouping of pods that are running on the cluster. Services are \"cheap\" and you can have many services within the cluster.","tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"Linux","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":377,"question":"The employees table has 20 records, what will be the output of the query SELECT gender FROM employees GROUP BY gender;","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"the query will return two rows only","answer_b":"the query will not return any records","answer_c":"the query will return 20 records","answer_d":"the query will generate an error message","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Hard"},{"id":633,"question":"What type of function is needed when passing values through a form or an URL?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"htmlspecialchars()","answer_b":"urlencode()","answer_c":"Both of these","answer_d":"None of the mentioned","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":624,"question":"What is the function file_get_contents() used for?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"file_get_contents() is used for reading a file and storing it in a string variable.","answer_b":"file_get_contents() is used for parsing a file and storing it in a string variable.","answer_c":"file_get_contents() is used for processing a file and storing it in a string variable.","answer_d":null,"answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"PHP"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":523,"question":"Which attribute can be used with BODY tag to set background color green?","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"background=\"green\"","answer_b":"bgcolor=\"green\"","answer_c":"vlink=\"green\"","answer_d":"None of above","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"true","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"HTML"}],"category":"Code","difficulty":"Medium"},{"id":907,"question":"This volume type can be used to share contents within containers in a pod, but will not persist beyond the life of a pod.","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"EmptyDir","answer_b":"Local","answer_c":"ConfigMap","answer_d":"FlexVolume","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"true","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"false","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":null,"explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"Kubernetes"}],"category":"DevOps","difficulty":"Easy"},{"id":367,"question":"Wildcards are","description":null,"answers":{"answer_a":"not supported by MySQL","answer_b":"characters such as % which perform single character matching","answer_c":"characters such as $ which perform pattern matches","answer_d":"used to perform pattern matches","answer_e":null,"answer_f":null},"multiple_correct_answers":"false","correct_answers":{"answer_a_correct":"false","answer_b_correct":"false","answer_c_correct":"true","answer_d_correct":"false","answer_e_correct":"false","answer_f_correct":"false"},"correct_answer":"answer_a","explanation":null,"tip":null,"tags":[{"name":"MySQL"}],"category":"SQL","difficulty":"Medium"}]